世上没有比确定哥更让我
There is nobody I would rather impress more
-想打动的人了  -太对
- than Sho Nuff. - ?True dat.
不  太对兄只是个DJ  我才懒得鸟他呢
No, True Dat's just the DJ. I don't care what he thinks.
想不到小卡和我是很好的舞伴
Turns out, Cam and I make tremendous dance partners.
我们的身体很合拍
Our bodies are so in tune,
就像是我们完成了彼此的
it's like we finish each other's...
动作
...sequences.
菲尔开始跳  我就本能地完成了
Phil starts a move, and I instinctually complete it.
对  就像听起来一样强大
And, yeah, it's as powerful as it sounds.
天啊  你有没有想过
Oh, my gosh. Did you ever think
来自密苏里州的农场男孩
a farm boy from Missouri
和来自佛州基韦斯特的房地产经纪人
and -- and a real-estate agent from Key West, Florida,
将得到去久负盛名的
would get the opportunity to audition
周二公司试跳的机会吗
for the prestigious Tuesday Company?
费用只比普通课程多一点
And it only costs slightly more than regular classes.